[{"__v": 0, "_id": "59784beb6072386304b07378", "answers": [{"answer": "getting", "id": "Lt9LR", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "47obo", "text": "making", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "lLTAZ", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:39.952Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784beb6072386304b07378", "question": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "2l01j", "text": "Read the paragraph and answer the questions", "type": "unstyled"}, {"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "63aad", "text": "My typical morning starts quite early, because I don’t like (1) ….. ready in a hurry.My alarm clock (2) ….. at 6.30, then I get (3) ….. and (4)….. downstairs in my dressing gown. I (5)….a cup of tea and (6) …..some breakfast.Then I (7)…..a shower and (8)….. my teeth.Then I get (9)….. ,(10) …. my hair and (11)….my make-up. Then I (12)…the bed and (13)….the washing up.If I’ve got time, I sometimes (14)….my email and (15)….the front page of the newspaper.I never  (16)….. TV in the morning. I usually (17) ….the house by 8.15.", "type": "unstyled"}, {"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [{"length": 31, "offset": 0, "style": "ITALIC"}, {"length": 31, "offset": 0, "style": "BOLD"}], "key": "ccq0v", "text": "Choose the verb to complete (1)", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.284Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784beb6072386304b0737a", "answers": [{"answer": "sounds", "id": "jCksv", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "2r5jg", "text": "goes off", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "hLWLz", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:39.980Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784beb6072386304b0737a", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (2)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.313Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784beb6072386304b0737c", "answers": [{"answer": "out of bed", "id": "jsG0V", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "ebate", "text": "from my bed", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "QIrLf", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:39.985Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784beb6072386304b0737c", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (3)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.319Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784beb6072386304b0737e", "answers": [{"answer": "walk", "id": "qQmPe", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "9sjv7", "text": "go", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "2Fmaw", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:39.989Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784beb6072386304b0737e", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (4)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.326Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784beb6072386304b07380", "answers": [{"answer": "do", "id": "bxA6x", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "6al4h", "text": "make", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "pudia", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:39.993Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784beb6072386304b07380", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (5)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.332Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784beb6072386304b07382", "answers": [{"answer": "have", "id": "1Sbsv", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "9st2t", "text": "eat", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "EG9rW", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:39.997Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784beb6072386304b07382", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (6)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.339Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b07384", "answers": [{"answer": "have", "id": "GeiCJ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "dek8n", "text": "use", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "joK06", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.001Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b07384", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (7)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.347Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b07386", "answers": [{"answer": "clean", "id": "9FxU5", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "f2rik", "text": "wash", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "Zuzjm", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.006Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b07386", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (8)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.353Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b07388", "answers": [{"answer": "clothed", "id": "Pdf8V", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "464dm", "text": "dressed", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "rQnhD", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.010Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b07388", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (9)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.359Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b0738a", "answers": [{"answer": "order", "id": "u41hH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "1pp1e", "text": "comb", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "TFCvO", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.013Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b0738a", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (10)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.366Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b0738c", "answers": [{"answer": "wear", "id": "fkV4l", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "2jb1l", "text": "put on", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "aSEAO", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.017Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b0738c", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (11)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.373Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b0738e", "answers": [{"answer": "do", "id": "qbOnh", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "9pvdu", "text": "make", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "tis5I", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.020Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b0738e", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (12)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.378Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b07390", "answers": [{"answer": "do", "id": "6U0Ht", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "23bf5", "text": "make", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "hf5vQ", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.024Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b07390", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (13)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.384Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b07392", "answers": [{"answer": "control", "id": "rTFHl", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "8t760", "text": "check", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "GN9Wy", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.028Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b07392", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (14)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.389Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b07394", "answers": [{"answer": "look at", "id": "Jx2Ob", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "3q8jr", "text": "watch", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "K6AI0", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.031Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b07394", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (15)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.399Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b07396", "answers": [{"answer": "see", "id": "oLI6r", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "fss76", "text": "watch", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "baxnE", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.037Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b07396", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (16)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.406Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b07398", "answers": [{"answer": "leave", "id": "hIBwY", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "e340r", "text": "depart", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "8XyAb", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.040Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b07398", "question": "Choose the verb to complete (17)", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.411Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b0739a", "answers": [{"answer": "usual", "id": "TJfYl", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "3vur", "text": "normal", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "EXBeS", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.044Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b0739a", "question": "Choose the right word You’re back-from holiday now,so I suppose it’s business as …..", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.417Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b0739c", "answers": [{"answer": "usual /special", "id": "P8Mnt", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "normal/ special", "id": "tr5HL", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "usual/ uncommon", "id": "x4kam", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "2tvco", "text": "normal/uncommon", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "ShnuK", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.047Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b0739c", "question": "Liz: How was the weekend ? Tom: Oh, the ….thing. Nothing ….", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.423Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b0739e", "answers": [{"answer": "began", "id": "eopRk", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "8d395", "text": "got into", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "e8KVA", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.051Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b0739e", "question": "I…. the habit of driking too much coffee when I went to Italy", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.430Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b073a0", "answers": [{"answer": "usual", "id": "mn91S", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "5hdkm", "text": "regular", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "QiegG", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.054Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b073a0", "question": "My husband wakes up at six o’clock, …. As clockwork", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.440Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59784bec6072386304b073a2", "answers": [{"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "7r9mt", "text": "break", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "5EyXJ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "5v9f1", "text": "end", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "question1501055950795", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-07-26T07:59:40.058Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "59784bec6072386304b073a2", "question": "Steve couldn’t …..the habit of lighting a cigarette after diner", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-07-26T11:46:58.446Z"}]